<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gists on gmagno</title>
    <link>https://gmagno.github.io/gists/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gists on gmagno</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gmagno.github.io/gists/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A quick look at fuel prices in Brazil</title>
      <link>https://gmagno.github.io/2019/11/a-quick-look-at-fuel-prices-in-brazil/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gmagno.github.io/2019/11/a-quick-look-at-fuel-prices-in-brazil/</guid>
      <description>On this post I share a link to a dashboard depicting the fuel prices thoughout the Brazil. The dataset used to generate the plots is provided by the brazillian government through ANP (Agência Nacional do Petróleo, Gás Natural e Biocombustíveis). Follows the link to the actual dashboard page: here.

@jonathanborba
   
The dashboard is WIP and at the moment tries to address three questions:
 How do fuel prices vary, in average, among distributors?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick setup of a proxyDHCP with dnsmasq and PXE boot</title>
      <link>https://gmagno.github.io/2019/05/quick-setup-of-a-proxydhcp-with-dnsmasq-and-pxe-boot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gmagno.github.io/2019/05/quick-setup-of-a-proxydhcp-with-dnsmasq-and-pxe-boot/</guid>
      <description>How to netboot a device in a few simple steps.

 @aligns
  
Since we will be relying on PXE, we need to ensure that our booting device has a network card that runs a PXE ROM, i.e it runs a firmware that implements some necessary internet protocols: UDP/IP, DHCP and TFTP.
We then need a DHCP server that is capable of replying to our device with both:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building python wheels for many linux-es</title>
      <link>https://gmagno.github.io/2019/01/building-python-wheels-for-many-linux-es/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gmagno.github.io/2019/01/building-python-wheels-for-many-linux-es/</guid>
      <description>Ever wondered how to build your python project and generate Linux binaries, aka wheels, that can be pulled from PyPI and run on any linux? Keep reading, you will be walked through in this brief post.

 @jontoney
  
Packaging and distributing is certainly one crucial step in the process of creating an app/lib. This is the moment you expose your app to the world, hopefully in a way that people can easily install.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>